http://www.photoreflect.com/mkt/privacypolicy.html

PhotoReflect (as a product of PhotoReflect LLC.) is
committed to protecting your privacy. Collected information is used to process
your orders and personalize your shopping experience. "Required Information" is
protected by secure server software. Photos are protected by standard online best practices and can additionally be protected by password and watermark per your selection (or request to your photographer) during the upload process.. We do not disclose your information
through sale, trade, or rent to others.
PhotoReflect
welcomes your input; e-mail:  support@photoreflect.com with questions
and comments.
Required Information
Photography Customers: Name, e-mail address, mailing address, daytime
phone number, credit card number, and expiration date are required for all orders. This allows us to process and fulfill your order and to notify you of
your order status.
Photographers: Name, e-mail address, mailing address and payment term
(either via direct deposit or check) details are required for all accounts. We
may use the information we collect to occasionally notify you of important
functionality changes to the Web site, new PhotoReflect services, and special
offers we think you'll find valuable. When you use the PhotoReflect PhotoCard
service, we ask for your e-mail address and that of the recipient in order to
complete your request.
Photographers may request Photo Customer email addresses for additional
information. PhotoReflect will never disclose or send promotional e-mail to
recipient addresses that belong to the Photographer or that are provided to the
PhotoReflect PhotoCard service.
Protecting Your Information
Photographers and Photography Customers: When placing orders or accessing
your account information, we offer the use of a secure server. The secure
server software (SSL) encrypts all information you input before it is sent to
us. Furthermore, all of the customer data we collect is protected against
unauthorized access. "Cookies" are small pieces of information that
are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Our cookies do not
contain any personally identifying information, but they do enable us to
provide features such as storage of items in your shopping cart between visits.
Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but in most cases you can
change this option in your Web browser.
Protecting Your Photos
Photography Customers: Your photos are organized into events that your
photographer can password-protect upon your request. Share your Event ID and
password only with those whom you wish to have access to your photos. Friends
and family will then have the ability to add your photos to their personal
online photo albums and/or order packages that are offered by your
photographer. Further, all enlarged representations of your photos on the
PhotoReflect.com Web site are digitally watermarked with either
"PhotoReflect.com" or your photographer's company logo embedded
directly into the images.
Any photos you upload to PhotoReflect are stored temporarily for the use of previewing and production of your selected products. The uploaded photos are not meant for sharing and will not be made available for public viewing. For your convenience we will keep your uploaded photos from your session for a short period of time to allow you to return to make your creative and buying choices. After such time the photos will be permanently deleted from PhotoReflect.
Photographers: Any sale of your photography is sold by your policies. You
are enabled to password protect events and watermark your photography as you
see necessary. The sale of Digital Delivery products enables you to sell your
clients digital images for their use. It is at your discretion to opt-in or out
of Digital Delivery as well as managing the formal rights of your photography
any further use beyond original intention.
Disclosure of Your Information
PhotoReflect's Privacy Policy prohibits selling, trading, or renting your
personal information to others. If the Privacy Policy changes to include
trustworthy third parties, we will notify you and offer you the opportunity to
refuse to share your information. Also, PhotoReflect may provide aggregate
statistics about our customers, sales, traffic patterns, and related site
information to reputable third-party vendors, but these statistics will not
include any personally identifying information.
